## Gjorgji Krstevski, Full Stack Developer

Kettering, United Kingdom, 07852275673, krstevskigj@gmail.com

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Game Development and Mobile Development
A life-long dedication to learning.
Effective at combining creativity and problem-solving to develop user-friendly applications.
Experienced in explaining technical stuff to a non-technical person.
Known for attention to detail and finding the right solution, no matter the complexity of the project.
Grasps new technologies and excels in teamwork, always ready to lend a hand.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Apr 2022 — Oct 2023

# Web Core and Mobile Developer, ServSuite, A FieldRoutes Company

Remote

#### Key Responsibilities:

- Collaborated with the Mobile Application Team and Production Team to ensure the seamless operation
  of web and mobile applications.
- Maintain legacy Mobile Application written with Action Script 3.0 and Flex framework.
- Conducted regular maintenance, addressing user requests and incorporating new features to enhance
  application functionality.
- Diagnosed and resolved bugs and issues to ensure a smooth user experience.
- Employed various technologies, including Vue.js, React.js, C#, VB.NET, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, HTML/CSS, SQL queries, and DevExpress, to create, optimize, and maintain applications.

May 2013 — Mar 2022

## Web Core and Mobile Developer, ServSuite

Remote

#### • Key Responsibilities:

- 1. Maintained web and mobile applications, ensuring their functionality and performance.
- 2. Added new features to web and mobile applications based on user requirements.
- 3. Diagnosed and fixed bugs and issues to enhance application reliability.
- 4. Conducted code refactoring to improve the maintainability and performance of applications.
- 5. Collaborated with multiple teams, including the Web Core Team, Red Code Team, Rollins, Reporting, Xamarin Mobile, and the traditional MA (AIR), Production Team.

#### · Technologies Used:

- 1. Developed mobile API using VB.NET and C#.
- 2. Worked on the core website using C# and VB.NET with Web Forms. NET.
- 3. Wrote SQL queries to support application functionality.
- 4. Used Xamarin (now .NET MAUI).

#### Notable Achievements:

• Led a small team from project inception through to the allocation of long-term development funding for a new mobile application built with Xamarin.

Jan 2009 — May 2013

## Independent Game Developer, Co-Founder, WootraGames

Skopje

Lead programmer and Team Leader, designing and developing games for the web, flash-based and mobile games.

(Please note that due to the nature of the technology, for the linked games to able to run, additional software is needed to be installed)

- Carveola Incident
- Fronts no Retreat
- Ambush
- <u>Ectology</u>
- Codename: Ballistic
- Sleepy Santa
- Oddo
- Carveola Files (no workable link)
- Carveola incident: 2118 A.D.(no workable link)
- A Tale of a Whisp (no workable link)
- Tech support: The Game (no workable link)

## Websites Developer, Independent Contractor

Skopje

• Key Responsibilities

Creating and maintaining numerous websites for local companies and a football club. This involved companies like:

- 1. DS Delivery
- 2. Konnello fast food
- 3. VIA Marketing
- 4. FC Metalurg Skopje

Sadly, no record of these websites remains since they stopped their activity a long time ago,

- Technologies used:
- 1. HTML/CSS
- 2. JavaScript
- 3. JQuery
- 4. MySQL
- 5. 5, PHP

Nov 2008 — Jan 2010

# Internet Provider Tech Support, On.net

Skopje

Answering calls, solving connection issues, setting WADSL connection, and remote receiver configuration.

## **EDUCATION**

## University of St. Cyril and Methodius

Degree in History

# High School Diploma, USO Brakja Miladonovci

SKILLS	Visual Basic .NET (Programming	g Expert	Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)	Expert
	Language)		Bootstrap (Front-End	Skillful
	JavaScript (Programming Language)	Expert	Framework)	
		Tii	Agile Software Development	Expert
	JavaScript ES6	Experienced	Android (Java)	Beginner
	C#	Experienced	PHP (Scripting Language)	Skillful
	SQL (Programming Language)	Expert	Xamarin	Skillful
	MySQL	Experienced	Git	Experienced
	Vue.js	Experienced	SVN	Experienced
	React.js	Beginner	TypeScrypt	Skillful
	Action Script 3.0	Expert	Agile/SCRUM	Experienced
	AS2	Skillful	119110, 0 0110111	1
	HyperText Markup Language (HTML)	Expert		
LANGUAGES	English	Highly proficient	Serbian	Highly proficient
	Macedonian	Native speaker	Croatian	Highly proficient